Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
Then, thus, a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Come aboard with me.
We're on Earth, a legendary.
If you can show your breath,
then we'll make some waves.
We're all not daunted, ain't no beginners.
Cause if you're wanted,
then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise.
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day.
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece, I'll be the first.
I'll put it so fast I could first.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on the wheel.
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward.
Keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very first day.
I'd make my name.
And don't you know that dream?
Hasn't changed.
I'm done playing through.
It's a wave in the air.
The world I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
And here we go!
We go!
Hurry up, we have to move!
We either get out of here
today or we die trying!
Come on, faster!
They'll be on top of us in minutes.
We'll never go back to Fishman Island.
Don't let up till we cross the Red Line.
Charlotte, I never got
to visit the Marine Cafe.
I never got to either.
It's such a waste.
You idiots get over it already.
Just shut up and keep rowing.
This whole thing is a disaster.
I thought we had made it after
we got past the sleeping kraken.
Then they ambushed us.
At 10,000 meters below.
And with so many sea monsters at their
disposal there was no
way to defend ourselves.
They told us we could join the new
fish man pirates or we could die.
As if they were really giving us a choice
at all who wouldn't pick life over death.
I told you all to get over it we're
lucky to even be alive right now.
Really they escaped I'm
afraid so boss humans
are always running for it
you'd think they would.
Have learned by now
cowardice is in their nature
you shouldn't let me chew
on them when I offered.
No it's good see now we
can use them as examples.
Then I'll go and drag them back.
So you can teach them their lesson.
Not this time you won't. Stay here.
If you say so boss.
I'll go myself.
You heard me.
Get the bubble ready.
Boss.
You can't take that
much power drug at once.
It's dangerous.
Home sweet home.
All right, shall we go in?
It's huge!
Welcome home, Master.
Can we get to anything?
Oh my gosh, Mr. Apopago.
As in the super famous designer?
I thought he'd be taller.
What are you talking about?
I live for this kind of attention.
When I'm in the water, I'm what
you'd call a fashionable starfish.
But on Fishman Island, I'm
so much more than that.
Seeing as I'm the president and lead
designer for criminal brand clothes.
The products we make are
coveted throughout the world.
No country is off limits
for our store chains.
Even Dosgoy Panda is...
What's that?
There's tons of people.
Wait, are you listening? Come on.
And the first floor is
a criminal brand store.
Cool.
I wasn't done talking.
You should go check it out.
Okay.
Wait, guys, what about my story?
Miss, I'm sorry, but I
can't accommodate you.
Giving you a discount like
that could cost me my job!
Sounds like someone is
causing them trouble.
People have some nerve.
Did you not hear me?
I don't care how cute
these clothes are They're
way too expensive Speaking
of nerve I want you
to cut the price to
10,000 berries But that's
less than half the retail
price You must understand,
I cannot do that It's just
as I thought, cheapskate
Hey, there you are, Nami
Luffy!
No!
Oh, hi, Kuma!
Oh, thank goodness you
showed up, Monsieur Papagu.
She wants half off,
just like her wardrobe.
So you're the one in charge
of this extortion ring?
You lower your prices, or
I'll lower you. Oh, Monsieur.
You see, there's a thing
called brand equity.
Because my designs are popular, they're...
I'm not listening.
Okay, okay, I get it!
Look, we're all friends here, aren't we?
I guess I owe you.
for all the help you
gave us two years ago.
Take as much as you can carry.
For real?
Why, thank you!
They took everything we had!
Aw, come on!
You can cut me some slack!
Talk about a deal!
Or steal.
My, what's all that racket?
Something serious must be happening.
Monsieur!
We have an emergency! What is it?
It's him!
He is here!
That's kind of vague.
I can't believe it.
Someone pinch me.
Up there in the sky, you can see him.
We're in the presence of royalty.
What the heck is that?
Some kind of whale?
What is he doing down
here in the lower world?
This is my first time seeing him.
This is unheard of.
He doesn't even have gold.
Something must be wrong in the kingdom.
That has to be it.
He never comes down here
unless there's an emergency.
The merman in front of you is
the king of the Ryugu kingdom,
the ruler of Fishman Island,
the god of the sea, Neptune!
Indeed I am.
Whoooooo!
Oh, wow.
Is this dude enormous or what?
I'd rather see a mermaid than a merman.
Will you two shut up?
He's super old, and he's
super hairy, too gross.
Keep your observations to yourself.
Kneel down and show some respect.
Can we talk about how cute the whale is?
Is he here because of the humans? Hmm.
Well, Megalo, are you certain these
are the people you encountered earlier?
Hold on. I know him.
We met that shark when we were outside.
Hear my words, Straw Hat people.
To the Ryugu Palace!
What?!
You're personally inviting
them to the palace!
Is that supposed to be a big deal?
Hurry up!
We gotta move! Roll faster!
That's why we should have equipped
ourselves with paddle wheels.
We weren't ready for
the new world after all.
Captain, look there.
There's something in the
water in front of us.
That's Heart Jones.
He found us.
We're screwed.
Hold on. See his hands?
Those are handcuffs.
Why is he stuck in those things?
Ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
He's gone!
Where the hell did he go?
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
What do we do now, boss? Take him out!
There's only one of them after all!
You're the first fish
man I fought against.
And I've done your dirty work.
Now it's my chance to
return the favor you're
only a damn fish so let
me teach you a lesson.
Don't mess with humans doctor no.
I'm not done yet.
Yeah you are we were tough before.
But we're unbeatable with this our
power drug the energy steroid fish
men are naturally ten times stronger
than humans but that hasn't made a
strong enough impression however
with just one pill we can double our
strength and finally strike some terror
into their cowardly little hearts.
I don't know if i'd go
as far as our boss but
doubling the dose and
doubling the effect has
its benefits, even if it
does shorten our lifespan.
Well, we aren't afraid of dying
if we can realize our dream, right?
Wait!
What the hell is he doing now?
Get away from
the mask, you freak!
That's why!
The handgun!
He warned him to prove that he doesn't use
hands to sink, guys!
Not only did humans kill Fisher Tiger,
but they also dashed Arlong's dreams.
The dark chain of events that
have cursed our race end now.
That is our purpose
as a new fishman pirate.
Set them adrift in the new world.
Okay but some of those guys are still
alive shouldn't we kill them all first
No they have a purpose you'll
see those of you who are getting
away with just cuts and bruises
Will live to send a message tell the
people up above what happened to
you in the sea Let them know who
did this to you you've seen my
strength firsthand so don't spare
a single detail Because once we've
liberated fish man island from
the gutless god of the sea neptune
we'll be coming To drag you
humans to the bottom of these
depths I promise you that and the
fish man will stand on Top of the
world as their supreme species!
Yeah!
A few hours before Luffy met with
King Neptune, something unexpected?
happened.
An unfortunate encounter
with a barrel at Mermaid
Cove.
Jeez, they sure sealed this thing tight!
It's packed up all nice like a.
treasure chest but it's still a barrel
so maybe some
fancy boots that'll
be enough just give me a second that's
right stand back thank you very much.
ladies but I think I can take it from
here you mean there was a person?
stuffed in there? No way!
I'm free!
Thank you so much for your help.
I truly couldn't have done it without you.
There's no need to run away.
Hurry!
Get to the water!
Too bad, too slow
What is this? I'm sinking.
It's mud.
But where did it all come from?
How very observant of you.
Though it's more like
quicksand technically.
Consider it my own personal swamp.
This is the power of
the swamp, swamp fruit.
Hardly glamorous, but I don't mind.
Oh, by the way.
I wouldn't struggle if I were you!
No!
That only makes you sink faster!
Someone help!
Oh, stop screaming!
I'm not gonna kill you!
I'll just suck you into a
mucky hellhole! Help me! What?
Are you brain-dead, lady?
I said stop screaming, didn't I?
Just give it up already!
Yes, you wait!
You're fine!
Calm down and take a nap, why don't you?
It's a good thing my
body's a bottomless pit,
since there's plenty more
treasure to put in it.
Let me think here, how
much do mermaids sell for?
70 million at auction, right?
And I nabbed three of them.
That is quite the catch, I must say.
Those stupid Straw Hats
help me out after all if it
gets me a free pass through
immigration you Can lock me
in a barrel anytime so what
if I plan to cash in on their
bounties didn't quite Pan
out now I can steal all the
mermaids I want the straw
hat pirates they must be the
ones who Kidnapped your
friends from Mermaid Cove who
else could it have been
hold on they saved Kuma from
kidnappers I'm sure you must
be mistaken they were nice they
aren't here to cause Any
trouble maybe they needed a
hostage but why first off let's
look at the facts excluding
us Guards and you mermaids
there was nobody else at
the cove around that time
and those thugs from The fish
man district were forced to
flee a number of the straw
hats left but a portion of
The crew is still unaccounted
for we don't know what
their intentions may be the
temptation for humans to kidnap
mermaids is just too great.
They're traded at a high
price all over the world,
and we have criminals like them to thank.
But they weren't just any pirates.
They saved Kuma from slavery.
Pirates often make friends with mermaids.
And then when they come down here,
they use that relationship to kidnap them.
Prince Fukaboshi.
Are you certain, Madam Charlie?
This vision that you saw,
it is of dire importance,
so I must be sure of its accuracy.
Your silence speaks volumes.
Then it is as you say, Straw Hat
will bring ruin to this island.
Here, Madam Charlie.
I brought you some water.
It's true.
I saw it all loud and clear.
Such an awful future.
The accuracy of your
predictions is well known.
I'm convinced that we must approach
this matter with the utmost caution.
It is quite the shame, though.
They seem to have a good
reputation with the mermaids,
and they saved my sister's pets,
so I wanted to treat them kindly.
But now that this new
development has come to light,
I fear that I must keep
a close eye on them.
We have no choice but to
take them all into custody.
They're gone.
Those weren't just ordinary
pirates, were they?
Otherwise,
King Neptune wouldn't have given them a
personal invitation to Ryugu Palace, huh?
Careful you don't fall.
Neptune.
Well.
Chachach.
Come on. What's J'mon?
Sounds dumb to me.
Kid, are you stupid or just play crazy?
You got invited to the royal palace.
Don't be a punk.
You have no idea how much my
daughter loves that shark.
It's her favorite pet.
Megalos never coming back, she
said, tears welling up in her eyes.
I had no idea that he'd
been attacked by the Kraken.
You have my gratitude for
rescuing him from danger.
I can't really take credit, but
whatever, it all worked out.
But the princess has a
shark for a pet, huh?
Oh, what's that, Papagoo?
Could it be that you're not as intimate
with the princess as you claim?
It did sound fishy.
Are you sure this is okay?
I mean, someone like me
going to Ryugu Palace.
He said we could bring our friends,
and you guys definitely make the cut.
By the way,
I sent my sons to fetch you, but they
took too long, and I grew impatient.
I hope they returned in the meantime.
We're holding a banquet, you see,
and I simply can't stand
to wait on any more guests.
I think we're going to get along great.
Gru, stop drooling!
Oh, speaking of guests, I already
invited one of your crewmates.
He's at the palace now.
Huh?
I must say he was a bit
lacking in manners, though.
He started drinking before the
banquet and wouldn't listen to
reason when I advised him to wait
for the other guests to arrive.
I seem to have forgotten his name.
Gotta be Zoro.
That's Zoro.
Saru!
It's Zoro, okay? Zoro!
Don't worry.
As surely as they found him,
my soldiers will find the rest of your
crew and bring them to the palace.
Hey, got any idea where
everyone else went, Nami?
Oh, uh...
If we ask around enough, I'm sure somebody
will have the info we're looking for.
Oh, yeah?
Then do you want to handle it?
If you're looking to shop, that's fine,
but I've got an errand of my
own I'd like to take care of.
This is where my old
shipwright master came from.
There's something I'd like
to see while we're here, too.
Oh, okay.
It's not often that I
get to explore a culture
that's completely removed
from the surface world.
Someone with a discerning
eye may uncover its secrets,
or even some pieces of
a forgotten history.
That's a Robin thing.
For sure.
So we split up again,
but it wasn't a big deal.
No trouble on your end, right?
Uh, well, maybe an itty-bitty bit.
Hey, Fish King, I have a question.
If we're 10,000 meters below sea level,
why is it so bright and
sunny everywhere we go?
Well, that's likely what our ancestors
thought when they first arrived here.
This is the only place in the
deep sea that light reaches.
It is a glorious glowing
beacon for all of fish
mankind and has been for as
long as anyone can remember.
We owe it all to the giant Sun Tree Eve,
whose mighty roots stretch to these depths,
carrying shimmering
sunlight along with them.
Sun Tree?
So are its roots bioluminescent, or does
it just transfer sunlight from the surface?
The latter, it seems, though scientists
have puzzled over the specifics for ages.
The respiration of its roots also supplies
oxygen from the surface to our island.
Regardless, we owe our entire
civilization to this single mystic tree.
So it's like the big
brother, or in this case,
big sister, of the mangroves in Sabaody.
Hey, hairy fish, dude, I'm
getting hungry. Come on!
We'll be there soon.
That's the entrance.
Get ready.
Ding Tang.
Yeah. Neptune.
Oh!
Hello, your highness!
Jesus, allow me to open the gate.
Land dwellers don't visit often, so much
of the palace is submerged in water.
We don't want anyone drowned.
Neptune!
It's fast!
Jamon, we're here.
Whoa!
Those dragons are sweet!
Hoppaka's house seems
positively shabby in comparison.
Hey, watch your mouth!
Buy me one of these, Luffy!
King Neptune has returned!
We were wondering where you ran off to.
Hurry, let them in!
Opening the gate.
Greetings, your highness.
Welcome back.
Now this is going to be fun.
Make yourselves at home.
You are my honored guests. Not again!
And you brought guests along.
I've told you not to leave
the palace on your own,
but you don't listen to a word I said.
If you can't take guards, and
you can't inform your staff,
then you can't leave the
palace, and that's final.
Shame on you, sir. Ja, Moon.
It won't happen again.
He got scolded?
There are so many countless
ways this could have gone wrong.
Our kingdom is in a volatile
political state right now.
Surely as a king, you realize that.
If you could stop scolding me,
you'll notice that I brought
back some very important people.
They're the pirates who
saved Megalo from the Kraken.
Let's welcome them properly
so I can maintain my dignity.
Where is Shirahoshi?
The princess should be here for this.
Actually, your highness,
we had another incident.
And she found out?
Don't give her another
thing to worry about.
She's a very delicate girl.
You know that.
Don't you give me that.
If you don't want your daughter to worry,
then how about you stay here in the palace
where it's safe instead
of running off unguarded.
We thought you might be dead.
It won't happen again.
I promise.
Wow. Again.
It's a bit unfortunate that
you brought the guest yourself.
There was a development while you were
out, and a rather troubling one at that.
Indeed.
Prince Fukaboshi called and informed us
of something better related and private.
Oh my goodness, this is quite awkward.
I trust our guests.
Out with it already.
That's the thing, sir.
So are we eating or hold on where'd
Luffy go yeah he was here just a
second ago he couldn't stand still
for five minutes if his life depended
on it this is the royal palace you
don't just wander around here on your
own can't smell anything now the food
must be through those giant doors?
Oh, this place looks pretty fancy.
It must be the banquet hall.
Let's hope Zoro hasn't
eaten all the good stuff.
But man, kind of intimidating, isn't it?
The doors are overkill.
I feel like I'm backing Impel down.
I really don't want people
getting their food, huh?
That must mean whatever they've
got in there is super good!
Huh?
It's dark. Why is it dark?
Well, who cares?
The food smells great.
Maybe it's going to be a surprise party.
Either way, I think
I've waited long enough.
A little snack will hurt.
What is this?
Feels like some kind of coral,
but why is it in a banquet hall?
Squishy again, weird
If someone's here, could
you turn on the lights?
Still really confused,
but this here is fun!
Hello, who's there?
What a horrid thing to do!
Bouncing on a poor, helpless
girl such as myself?
Who are you, sir, and
what are you doing here?
Please don't hurt me.
Whoa!
That's one big lady!
I mean, big fish lady.
Have you come to kill me, too?
Because I will have you now.
I'm not afraid.
No, not of you.
Not of anyone else, either.
I am the daughter of King Neptune.
I'm not, I'm not afraid of anything.
Nothing at all.
Someone help me!
Mother, please!
Hey, wait!
We didn't come here to kill you, okay?
You suck, lady!
Shut up already!